发薪日到了 我不是在说
It's payday. And I'm not talking about
那个好吃带小花生[蛋蛋]的坚果棒哦
the delicious little treat with nuts.
阿憨 这么自吹自擂可不对哦
Han, not cool to brag about yourself
给 麦克斯 拿着钱去买新态度吧
Here, Max, maybe you can use the money to buy a new attitude.
"新态度"
"New attitude"?
这不是你的基男团体的名字吗
Isn't that the name of the boy band you're in?
奥列格 你会发现我扣了你钱
And Oleg, you'll notice I docked your pay
因为你昨天压根没来上班
'cause you didn't even come in yesterday.
我跟你说了 我在家工作
I told you, I was working from home.
给你 厄尔
There you go, Earl.
别全花到一处去了
Don't spend it all in one place.
你觉得你给的这点薪水够我花到两处吗
You think you pay me enough to spend it in two places?
天啊 这比我今天来上班的交通费还少
Oh my God, this is less than it cost me to get here today.
我还是用走的呢
And I walked.
对啊
I know!
我薪水就这么点吗
That's all I made?
这算啥啊 "为奴婢12年"吗
What's this? "12 years a waitress"?
你是"一班12瓶酒"吧
With you, it's more like "12 beers a shift."
大话真多
So many words,
其余皆小
so little everything else.
放过我的脸
Not the face!
放过我的俏脸
Not my beautiful face!
我警告你 我以前跳过《胡桃夹子》[破蛋蛋者]
I warn you, I was in the nutcracker suite.
-什么意思 -这意思
- What's that mean? - This!
麦克斯 别担心 我搞定他了
Don't worry Max, I handled it.
是啊 我也刚"搞"定他 他是我炮友
Yeah, I just handled it too. That's my booty call.
你的意思是你认识他吗
Are you telling me you know him?
我不认识他
No, I don't know him.
他只是每周二晚上来打炮而已
He just comes over for sex on Tuesday nights.
需要我扶你起来吗
Do you need help up?
等会 我的眼泪还在吧嗒掉呢
Not yet, I'm still crying a little.
好了 起来走人吧
Okay, up you go.
走两步就没事了
Walk it off.
好啦 我知道很疼
Yeah, I bet that hurts.
你真行啊 卡洛琳 最赞的"部分"被你毁了
Nice going Caroline. You ruined the best part.
我叫卡洛琳 她室友兼首席女芭蕾舞员
Hi, I'm Caroline, the roommate and prima ballerina.
抱歉伤到了你的"仙桃"
Sorry about your sugar plums.
塞巴斯安
Sebastian.
停停停 不许说名字 不许
Ba-ba-ba! No names! No names!
卡洛琳 要过来喝杯汽水吗
Uh, Caroline, you want a soda?
我们家有汽水吗
We have soda?
白痴 我们家当然没汽水
No, we don't have soda!
你干嘛问他名字啊
Why are you asking him his name?
他不想知道我名字 我也不想知道他名字
He doesn't wanna know my name and I don't wanna know his.
不介意我用一下你们洗手间吧
Hey, mind if I use your bathroom?
我想去检查下蛋弟弟
I need to check on the boys.
怕都变蛋花妹了
See if they're girls.
你怎么能不知道"亲密"对象的名字呢
How do you not know the name of the guy you're intimate with?
亲密咧
"Intimate"?
麦克斯 在你跟一名男性
Max, there are certain things you have to know
发生性爱关系前 你得对他有一定认识啊
about the guy you're engaging in sexual congress with.
只有你能把打炮弄得无聊
Only you can make sex boring.
不算太惨
Well, not too bad.
一颗没事 另一颗得坐轮椅了
One's okay and the other one left on crutches.
先走啦
Later.
塞巴斯安 等等
Sebastian, wait.
她叫麦克斯·布莱克
This is Max Black.
麦克斯 他叫塞巴斯安
Max, this is Sebastian.
幸会 麦克斯
Nice to meet you, Max.
是啊 幸会幸会
Yeah, nice to meet you too.
你像平常那样称呼我就行了
And you can just call me what you usually do.
"哇 爽呆了"
"Oh, God."
厄尔 那件是新衣服吗
Hey is that a new shirt, Earl?
是啊 麦克斯 我1987年买的
Why, yes it is, Max. I just got it in 1987.
这下好了 你看这条短信
Oh, great! Look at this text.
来自精虫数量被你降低的仁兄
It's from the guy whose sperm count you lowered.
他叫塞巴斯安
His name is Sebastian.
他邀请你去看他打碟呢
Oh, he's inviting you to come see him DJ.
妈的 我就告诉你我不想认识他
Oh, damn it! I told you I didn't wanna know anything about him,
现在我知道他是DJ了
and now I know he's a DJ.
等于他是个无业游民 这倒是加分点
Which means he unemployed, so points for that.
你打算怎么回复他
So what are you gonna text him back?
不回
Nothing!
我跟他唯一会"来回"的不是短信
The only back-and-forth I want from this guy
而是他"来"躺下面 我"回"上面爽四次
is on his back and for the fourth time.
秘密性爱才是最棒的性爱
The best sex is secret sex.
是"秘密"就不要在我吃饭的时候说
Then maybe don't talk about it while I'm eating.
我有个性感秘密
Well, I have a sexy secret.
我暗恋某姑娘
A crush on a girl.
奥列格 鬼都知道你暗恋我
Oleg, we all know it's me.
你裤裆对我的"敬礼"出卖了你
That sweat-pant salute never lies.
不是你 别傻了
Not you. Don't kid yourself.
本狼在床上一生没遇过对手
You couldn't handle this beast in the sheets.
奥列格 我在床上绝对把你治到服服帖帖
I could totally handle you in the sheets, Oleg.
卡洛琳 你争这个是什么意思啊
What are you fighting for, Caroline?
大家安安
Hey, everybody!
来 报告外面天气
All right, weather report:
我刚跟人约完会 废柴多如雨点
I just came back from a date and it's raining losers out there.
我性感诱人的秘密暗恋对象来了
There's my sexy, sexy, secret crush.
谁 苏菲吗 秘密个屁啊
Who, Sophie? Not so secret.
你们在布鲁克林所有公共场合都"做"过了吧
You two have already done it in every public space in Brooklyn.
对啊 在你家也做过两回呢
Yeah, and your apartment, twice.
干嘛 我们都没吵醒你啊
What? We didn't even wake you!
苏菲 我的宝贝儿
Sophie, baby,
众里寻她千百度
I've been looking for the perfect woman
蓦然回首 那人只在我的"后门"处
And it turns out, what I want is in my own back door.
后庭
Backyard.
你们俩好像说得都对
I think you're both right.
你"送货"的声音我听见了
I hear your truck pull up.
但我不知道还想不想签收你裆里的货
But I'm not sure I wanna sign for your package anymore.
我就知道你会这么说
I knew you were going to say that.
为了提醒你
So as a reminder,
我给你做了张我们的性爱特辑
I've created a sizzle reel of our best sex.
是性"病"特辑吧
So it's an STDVD?
这是加"长"版
It's the extended version.
一刀未"割" 你懂的
Uncut, as you know.
够了 把我点的布朗尼取消吧
That's it, cancel my brownie!
特辑吗
Sizzle reel?
我今晚吃我的墨西哥卷时边吃边看吧
I'll watch it tonight while I eat my fajitas.
麦克斯 塞巴斯安又给你发短信了
Max, you just got another text from Sebastian.
谁啊
Who?
麦克斯 我们去他的舞厅看他打碟好吗
Please, can we go to the club to see him DJ, Max?
我好想跳舞
I wanna dance.
我上一次甩动屁股
The last time I shook my booty
还是因为家里厕纸用完了呢
was when we ran out of toilet paper.
麦克斯 谢谢你带我来跳舞
Max, thank you so much for taking me dancing.
你都签了那张如果我带你来
Well, you signed that paper that said if I did,
你就帮我做六个月店里杂工的契约了
you'd do the side work for the next six months.
你确定这里就是塞巴斯安
Are you sure this is the address
告诉你的舞厅地址吗
of the club Sebastian gave you?
谁啊
Who?
塞巴斯安
Sebastian!
地址肯定不是这里 这里是全食超市呢
This can't be the address. It's a Whole Foods.
我知道这是哪
I know what it is.
从这里就能闻到"散养"人味儿
I can smell the cage-free body odor.
我们就进去问人 看有谁知道舞厅在哪
Let's just go in, ask someone if they know where the club is,
然后顺便偷拔一小串葡萄 我好饿啊
and maybe rip a grape off a stem--I'm starving.
全食超市呢
Whole Foods, wow.
让我想起来我还是个"全"人的时候
Reminds me of when I was a whole person.
麦克斯 我们不用找舞厅了
Max, we can stop looking for the club.
来吧 来吧
All right, all right.
节奏超有哏 快买甜菜根
I'm gonna lay down some beats while you check out our beets.
有机的哦
Organic!
你看
See?
这就是为什么我什么都不想知道
This is why I didn't want to know anything!
你问了炮友的名字
You ask a guy his name
然后就发现他在水萝卜旁打碟
and you find out he's DJ'ing next to radishes.
而且是怎样的废柴会来这跳舞啊
And what kind of loser comes here to dance?
哈啦
Holla!
我不是说犹太面包"哈拉"哦
And I don't mean the kosher bread!
靠 你们怎么发现我在这的
Oh, no. How did you find me here?
全食超市是我的性感秘密
Whole Foods is my sexy secret.
你知道什么不是秘密吗
You know what's not a secret?
你菜篮里的有机痔疮膏
The organic preparation H in that basket.
全食超市是我想摇摆时来的地方
Whole Foods is where I come to get my groove on.
为什么 儿童游戏机房关了吗
Why? Is Chuck E. Cheese closed?
虽然我很想留下看你会买什么
As much as I'd love to see what else you're gonna buy
好一件一件羞辱你 但我们要走了
to rub on your butt, we're leaving
我不想被那DJ看到
Before that DJ sees me.
你是说"新鲜本地"DJ先生吗
You mean DJ Fresh-and-Local?
音乐顶呱呱 大家买南瓜
The music be bumpin' and we buyin' pumpkins!
走吧 真不敢相信我穿了"战袍"来看这个
Let's go. I can't believe I wore these for this.
起来
Wake up.
今天是周二 那DJ没"来"
It's Tuesday, and the DJ didn't come.
他可能酒喝多了 不行了吧
Maybe he just drank too much.
不是 是没"来"找我
No! He didn't show at all.
新鲜本地DJ先生来没来玩我的"1 2号碟"
There's no DJ fresh-and-local in my ones and twos.
那你要怎么样
Well, what did you expect?
你那天招呼都没打就跑掉了
You ran out of there without even saying "Hi."
我们那天应该留在那舞厅的
We should've stayed at the club.
不许再叫那里舞厅
Stop calling it a club!
他在超市里打碟
He DJs at a supermarket,
这是我这辈子见过最弱爆了的事情
which is the lamest thing I've ever seen,
虽然比不上你
not counting the time
想复活过时几百年的流行语
you tried to bring back the phrase
"你特么在逗我吗"
"Oh, no, you didn't."
我真不敢相信你会这样
I'm surprised at you.
如果是我鄙视你以前做过的工作呢
What if I judged you for some of your jobs?
你敢说我以前当墨西哥湾里的
Uh, bar-back slash captain of a shrimp boat
补虾船船长兼吧台助理不屌吗
in the gulf of Mexico isn't the bomb?
你以前在烂大街服饰店盖璞工作过呢
What about when you worked at the Gap?
谁告诉你盖噗的事的
Who told you about the Gap?
你自己啊 你有一次喝醉酒 在折件毛衣
You, that time you were drunk, folding a sweater,
你说 让你推荐一下招牌休闲短裤来
and you tried to help me "spring into summer"
"甩开春天 迎接夏天"
with cargo shorts.
行 我是跳入盖噗[火坑]过 当时需要钱
Fine! I fell into the Gap. I needed the money.
或许塞巴斯安也是需要钱啊
Maybe Sebastian needs the money, too.
谁啊
Who?
如果你敢告诉别人我在盖噗的事
And if you ever tell anyone about the Gap,
你的原来项上人头之处
you will have a gap between your neck
也会变成大坑[盖噗]
and where your head used to be.
"你特么在逗我吗"
"Oh, no you didn't."
我本来不确定会不会打扰你们睡觉
Hey, I wasn't sure if it was too late to come by
但是我的碟仙板指示"去吧 她们还没睡"
but the Ouija board said, "Go ahead, the girls are up!"
你信这个啊
You use that?
我唯一信的仙 是廉价酒中仙
The only spirit I listen to is 2-buck-chuck,
而这色老头总是叫我脱掉上衣
and he mostly tells me to take my top off.
碟仙帮助我做了很多重大决定
Yeah, Ouija helps me make all my big decisions.
比如来美国
Like coming to America,
收养一个中国孤儿
adopting a Chinese orphan,
以及把那中国孤儿丢到消防局
and leaving a Chinese orphan at the fire station.
这东西超诡异
Those boards are creepy.
你永远不知道请到的是仙是鬼
you never know what you're inviting in.
万一请到深渊巨口怎么办
I mean, what if we open a hellmouth?
拜托 姑娘们 看看你们四周
Aw, come on, girls, look around.
你们已经在地狱之中啦
I mean, you already have.
现在安静 来吧
Okay, now shh. Okay...
碟仙
Ouija,
我是否该跟奥列格复合呢
should I take Oleg back?
是
Yes?
你们看 太吓人了
Oh, now, see, that is creepy
我刚才一直想推到"否"呢
because I was shoving it to "No".
你想跟他复合吗
Do you want to get back with him?
我很左右为难
Well, I'm torn.
而且我也不知道该怎么做
And also, I don't know what to do.
把手放在空中甩 把甘蓝都买起来
Throw your hands in the air like you just don't kale.
我很高兴你能够不介意他的工作
Max, I'm proud of you for overlooking his job
给人家一次机会
and giving this guy a chance.
他在装那副DJ脸 我看不下去了
He's making a DJ face. I'm out.
天啊 迪伦
Oh, my God, Dylan.
我们不能现在走
No, we can't leave now.
我刚看到了
I just saw this girl,
这世上我最不想见到的人
and she is the last person I want to see.
你跟她是怎么回事
What is the problem?
是 希拉里·沃德尔
It's Hilary Waldare.
我们以前一起在沃顿读书
We went to Wharton together.
她超爱跟我比较
So competitive with me.
当我家破产时 她超幸灾乐祸
Loved it when I lost all my money.
她还特别办了一个派对庆祝
She even threw a party to celebrate
而且她还有种到邀请我去
and then had the nerve to invite me.
对了 她那派对瞎到爆
Worst party ever, by the way.
有比位在一家超市里的舞厅还瞎吗
Uh, worse than being at a dance club that has a price club?
麦克斯·布莱克来到了麦子之家
Max black in the house of grain.
而且被他看到我了
And now he saw me.
我得在她看到我之前先躲起来
Well, I'm gonna go hide before she sees me.
我去汤姆斯布鞋店躲着 那里从没人去
I'll be in Tom's shoes. Nobody's ever over there.
给大家"带来"我散养的电子舞曲
I'm bustin' out some free range electronic dance music.
没错
That's right!
用我自带的购物袋"带来"的哦
I'm bringing it in my own bag.
好了 我们没问题吧
Uh, okay, we good?
下周二见
See you next Tuesday.
别这样 留下 干嘛这么急
Come on, stay. What's your hurry?
我看不下这些人边跳边逛了
I can't watch any more people dance-shop.
麦克斯 来嘛 来我前面
Max, come on. Get in front of me.
看看你有啥招
See what you can do.
这次你到我后面了 挺新鲜
Oh, you're behind me this time--that's new.
好了 各位
All right, everybody,
苦苣[别动] 我们来了特别来宾DJ哦
Frisee, 'cause we got a special guest DJ in the hizzay
辣到有辣椒这么辣哦
who's so hot it's radicchio.
来吧
Go on.
鲍伯 我想下注一块钱
Bob, I'd like to bid $1.00.
一块钱 鲍伯 一块钱
$1.00, Bob, $1.00.
请带您的宠物做绝育手术
Have your pets spayed or neutered.
说到绝育后的宠物 阿憨在这里哦
Speaking of neutered pets, here comes Han.
这照样算是DJ喊话哦
Still counts as a DJ shout-out.
为什么要等到周二
Hey, why wait till Tuesday?
何不我直接休息一下 然后我们去后面
Why don't I take a break and we can go in the back.
只需找一个人顶替我就行了
I just need to find someone to cover me.
有人把果仁酱全买完了
Someone bogarted all the nut butter.
找"半个人"顶替你行吗
How about half of someone?
需要帮忙吗 小姐
Can I help you, Miss?
麦克斯
Max?
你这是干什么
What are you doing?
口渴难耐 家财散尽
I'm thirsty, broke,
试喝柠檬水的人也不许我再喝了
and they cut me off at the free lemonade.
你又在干什么
What are you doing?
两男的抢先在亲子厕所里开搞了 所以...
Well, two dudes were getting it on in the family restroom, so...
塞巴斯安呢
Where's Sebastian?
谁啊
Who?
他啊 架子下面放牛奶那
Oh, milk. Bottom shelf.
你好啊
What's up?
不许在乳制品货架后面开搞
You're not doing it in the dairy case!
我才没有呢 因为你在这碍事
Uh, no I'm not, 'cause you won't go away.
为什么在哪你都要坏我"好事"啊
Do you have to ruin sex everywhere?
麦克斯 就算我以前没有乳糖不耐症
Well, Max, if I wasn't lactose intolerant before,
现在也有了
I am now.
天啊 这不是卡洛琳·钱宁吗
Oh, my God, Caroline channing!
你好啊 我是希拉里·沃德尔
Hi! It's Hilary Waldare.
-天啊 你好 -你好
- Oh, my God! Hi! - Hi!
自从派对之后 我就没见过你了
I haven't seen you since your party.
听说你是哭着离开的 最近过得好吗
Someone said you left crying. How are you?
非常好 我专门来全食超市
I'm great! I mean, I'm shopping at Whole Foods,
买点有机营养奶
buying some organic fuel
我可能就在动感单车课上小酌一两口
that I'll probably take a couple sips of in spin class
然后整瓶扔掉
and then throw away, so...
那就好 因为我听说你穷得叮当响
Oh, good, 'cause I heard you were still poor
迫于生计只能当个服务员
and that you were working as a waitress.
服务员
A waitress?
一派疯言
That is insane.
简直疯到
That is so insane
应该扔进精神病院的冰浴缸里
it should be in an ice tub in an asylum.
你过得好就好
I'm so glad you're great,
因为当我看见你穿着三年前的旧款名牌鞋时
because when I saw you in those three-year-old Louboutins,
我不禁担心起来
I got worried.
对了 你嘴唇上方有橙汁印
Also, you have an orange juice mustache.
是你啊 麦克斯呢
Oh. Where's Max?
牛奶那
Milk.
-麦克斯 听我说 -忙着呢
- Max, listen-- - Busy!
希拉里还没走呢
Hilary's still here.
她刚说我是服务员 好大的胆子
And she called me a waitress. How dare her.
她羞辱了我 而且这次连个派对都没有
She humiliated me, and I didn't even get a party this time.
我要回家了
I'm going home.
希拉里·沃德尔 请到3号收银台报到
Hilary Waldare, report to register three.
老天 广播是喊...
Oh, my God! Did he just say--
希拉里·沃德尔 请到3号收银台
Hilary Waldare. Register three.
果然是她 麦克斯 我要翻盘了
He did! Oh, my God! Max!
忙着呢
Busy!
干嘛 你阴魂不散是想加入我们吧
What? Do you wanna just join us?
希拉里·沃德尔在这里上班 她是收银员
Hilary Waldare works here, as a cashier!
我赢了
So I win!
人人都知道工作丢人链的顺序是这样
Everyone knows on the job humiliation chain, it goes:
妓女 舞女 服务员
Prostitute, hostess, waitress,
收银员 迪斯尼彩灯巡游的茉莉公主
cashier, Princess Jasmine in the Disney electric light parade.
你不是说就算别人的工作很垃圾
What happened to not looking down
也不应该看不起人家吗
on other people with crappy jobs?
那是假道理 这是真人生
Oh please, this is real.
我口袋里的14块心急如"焚"到
Now if you'll excuse me, I have got $14
要把口袋烧出个洞了
burning a second hole in my pocket,
我得去羞辱她了 3号收银台我来啦
and I'm gonna spend it here at register three.
靠 你就不能等等我[高潮]吗
What, you couldn't wait for me?
这首歌送给预加工食品处的凯丽
This goes out to Kelly in prepared foods.
是长痤疮的凯丽小姐
The Kelly with the cystic acne,
不是秃顶的凯利先生哦
Not the Kelly with the bald spot.
愛黛兒的粉丝站出来
Now, where my Adele-heads at?
太好了 你这没人排队
I'm glad you have no line,
因为我要赶着上一对一的私教瑜伽课
'cause I have an exclusive private yoga class to get to--
希拉里
Oh, Hilary!
你好 卡洛琳
Yes, Caroline.
我是一名收银员
I am a cashier.
抱歉 我没听清
I'm sorry, a what?
我是一名收银员
I'm a cashier.
没错 我的生活并不如意
Yeah, turns out things aren't great.
我老公为了我爸离开了我
My husband left me for my dad.
把故事版权卖给生活电影台时 钱也没分我
And they didn't even cut me in on the Lifetime Movie rights.
一月份就上映了
It's on in January--
片名是《新娘是岳父》
Father Is the Bride.
我帮你把沙拉过称吧
Let me just weigh your salad.
我相信你一定会像我一样 很快振作起来
Well, I'm sure you'll pull yourself together like I did.
因为我现在日子过得得心应手
'cause I'm kind of killing it, life-wise.
应该是28美元
That'll be $28.
这里只有14美元
There's only $14 here.
一盒沙拉要28美元
$28 for a salad?
这是恐龙甘蓝
Well, that's dinosaur kale.
那我拿错了
Oh! Mistake.
我不要恐龙甘蓝
Didn't want the dinosaur kale.
我不喜欢过时的恐龙 我的甘蓝里也不许有
Never liked dinosaurs and really don't like them in my kale.
恐龙甘蓝都拿掉了
Dinosaur kale gone.
你不过是拿出来放在柜台上
You're just putting it on the counter?
我一般不亲自出来买东西
Oh, I don't usually shop for myself.
这样放不对吗
Is that not how it's done?
卡洛琳 你是不是不够钱结账呀
Caroline, do you not have enough money?
不 希拉里 我够钱结账哦
No, Hilary, I have enough money.
我只是不知道为什么会有这么多鸡蛋
I just don't know why I have so many eggs.
钱还你 你妨碍后面排队的人了
Here. You're holding up the line.
显然你不够钱结账
You obviously don't have enough money
买不起这盒沙拉
to pay for your salad.
真可悲
Sad.
我不知道你这话是什么意思
I don't know what you're implying.
这位是我非常成功的生意合作伙伴
Oh! Here is my very successful business partner.
抱歉让你久等了 刚才找了好久裤子
Sorry it took so long. I couldn't find my pants.
都不知道我裤子是怎么跑到装货区的
I don't know how they made it all the way to the loading dock.
承认吧 卡洛琳 你是来羞辱我的
Face it Caroline, you came here to humiliate me
结果丢人到付不起鸡蛋
and you can't even afford that egg.
真是丢死人
On your face.
小姐 这张20块是你掉的吗
Miss, did you drop this $20 bill?
对 没错 是我掉的
Yes! Yes I did!
我也掉了点钱
I dropped some money, too.
别得寸进尺
Don't push it.
谢谢你 先生 你人真好
Thank you, sir. This is very kind of you
真是太感谢你了
And I really appreciate it.
我愿为我最喜欢的服务员效劳
Anything for my favorite waitress.
我就知道你是个服务员
Oh, I knew you were a waitress.
你的店烂爆了
Your store sucks!
我刚在乳制品货架后做爱了
I just had sex in your dairy department.
不用找了
Keep the change.
就当是送你老爸老公的结婚礼吧
And buy your dad-husband a wedding gift.
好 再来一次
Okay, one more time.
碟仙 我是否该跟奥列格复合
Ouija, should I be with Oleg?
试了15次 次次皆"是"
15 out of 15 yeses.
还是不够清楚
That's still unclear.
苏菲 问碟仙蠢爆了
Sophie, this is silly.
你知道你们俩都想复合
You know you two wanna get back together.
卡洛琳 我们已经有碟仙板了
Caroline, we already have the Ouija board.
这里不需要多一样又扁又平
We don't need another thing around here that's flat
还每次都错的玩意
and wrong all the time.
好吧 苏菲 我付出那么多
Fine. Sophie, if it's not me,
你还不愿意复合 那你走吧
after all I've offered you, go.
问问碟仙 你该跟谁在一起
Ask the spirits who the man you are supposed to be with is.
碟仙 我该跟谁在一起
Ouija, please spell out the name of the man
请把他的名字拼出来
that I'm supposed to be with.
瞧 动了
Oh, look, it's moving.
V A N[万]
"V," "A," "N,"--
没有互联网之前 世界就是这样的
This is what the world was like before the internet.
K O[科]
"K," "O."
"万科"
"Vanko."
万科这名字不错
Vanko? Yeah, that sounds cute.
我喜欢 抱歉 奥列格
Yeah, I like it-- I'm sorry, Oleg.
碟仙都发话了
The spirits have spoken.
我应该跟名叫"万科"的男人在一起
I'm supposed to be with someone named Vanko.
碟仙知道谁最适合我
And they know the best.
所以你应该跟名叫"万科"的男人在一起吗
So you're supposed to be with someone named Vanko?
"万科·奥列格·高列彻夫斯基"
"Vanko Oleg Golishevsky"?
我一直用中间名
I go by my middle name
是因为我家已经有七个叫"万科"的了
'cause there were seven other Vankos in my family.
但我本来不知道啊
But I didn't even know that.
这就意味着碟仙...
Yeah, that means the Ouija is--
还真是啊
Ohh...yeah...
不 不 我不要万科
Oh, no, no, Vanko. No!
不要 不要
I-- no, I--no!
我们可以复合 好吗
We can--you and I can get back together, okay?
但我现在不想待在这里
But I just can't be here right now.
我是说 这玩意太他妈吓人了
No, I mean, this is just too damn spooky!
我迫不及待想告诉我的兄弟
I can't wait to tell my brothers,
万科哥和万科弟这个消息
Vanko and Vanko, about this.
道上有传言说
Word on the street is
你俩很鄙视当收银员的啊
you've been talking some smack about cashiers.